<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Transportation GIS Projects</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Transportation GIS Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2020, Amin keramati</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Highway-Rail Grade Crossing Safety</title>
      <link>/post/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Project Abstract Map Digitizing Nearest Intersection &amp;amp; Crossing Smallest Crossing Angle Computational Results HRGC Geometric Effect Calculator Related Publication  
Project Abstract Highway-rail grade crossings (HRGCs) are where a roadway and railway intersect at the same level.Safety at HRGCs has been identified as a high-priority concern among transportation agencies, but there has been little research on the effects of HRGC geometric parameters on their safety performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Log-Truck Transportation Analysis</title>
      <link>/post/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Project Abstract Data and Methodology 2.1. Study area (Step a) 2.2. GIS database (Step b) 2.3. Road Maintenance Scenarios (Step c) 2.4. Road Network Analysis (Step d)  Related Publication  
Project Abstract Wood transportation costs have significant impacts on timber investment returns. To optimize transportation costs, a practical design of the route network is necessary for log-trucks that ship wood material from timberlands to wood mills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>/post/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>