<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Transportation GIS Projects</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Transportation GIS Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2020, Amin Keramati</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Highway-Rail Grade Crossing Safety</title>
      <link>/post/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Project Abstract Map Digitizing Nearest Intersection &amp;amp; Crossing Smallest Crossing Angle Computational Results HRGC Geometric Effect Calculator Related Publication   
Project Abstract Highway-rail grade crossings (HRGCs) are where a roadway and railway intersect at the same level.Safety at HRGCs has been identified as a high-priority concern among transportation agencies, but there has been little research on the effects of HRGC geometric parameters on their safety performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Log-Truck Transportation Analysis</title>
      <link>/post/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Project Abstract Data and Methodology 2.1. Study area (Step a) 2.2. GIS database (Step b) 2.3. Road Maintenance Scenarios (Step c) 2.4. Road Network Analysis (Step d)  Related Publication   
Project Abstract Wood transportation costs have significant impacts on timber investment returns. To optimize transportation costs, a practical design of the route network is necessary for log-trucks that ship wood material from timberlands to wood mills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bike Route Choice Modeling Analysis</title>
      <link>/post/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Project Abstract Data Methodology   
Project Abstract In this project, I executed several python scripts and GIS models to allow map-matching of more than 14,000 bike GPS points to the Downtown Toronto street network. These data are using as part of the project titled &amp;#34;Bike route choice modeling analysis&amp;#34;.  
Data The GPS points in this project indicate several number of specific routes which are passed by several number of bike riders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRGC Geometric Effect Calculator</title>
      <link>/post/calc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/calc/</guid>
      <description>Click on the figure to run the calculator: 
 Explanations: HRGC geometric effect calculator is an application designed to predict crash occurrence and severity likelihood changes over 30 years. The calculator works based on the Competing Risk Models which is one of the survival analysis approach, and it is counted as a novel model in transportation safety analysis. Please refer here for more details about the model. Through this online application, you can change the geometric characteristics of the highway-rail grade crossing and see how these changes effect on crash occurrence and severity changes over 30-year time span with an interactive plot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>